[
    {
        "id": 112,
        "question": "What is the difference between GET and POST method?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "GET displays the form values entered in the URL of the address bar where as POST does not.",
            "answer_b": "POST displays the form values entered in the URL of the address bar where as GET does not.",
            "answer_c": "There is no difference",
            "answer_d": null,
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "PHP"
            }
        ],
        "category": "",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_a"
    },
    {
        "id": 98,
        "question": "Can echo in PHP accept more than 1 parameter?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "True",
            "answer_b": "False",
            "answer_c": null,
            "answer_d": null,
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "PHP"
            }
        ],
        "category": "",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_a"
    },
    {
        "id": 62,
        "question": "What is the correct way to end a PHP statement?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": ";",
            "answer_b": "New line",
            "answer_c": "</php>.",
            "answer_d": null,
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "PHP"
            }
        ],
        "category": "",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_a"
    },
    {
        "id": 756,
        "question": "Which of the following type of variables have only two possible values either true or false?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "Integers",
            "answer_b": "Doubles",
            "answer_c": "Booleans",
            "answer_d": "Strings",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "PHP"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Code",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_c"
    }, {
        "id": 605,
        "question": "How can you pass a variable by reference?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "$var1 = &$var2",
            "answer_b": "$var1 == &$var2",
            "answer_c": "$var1 === &$var2",
            "answer_d": null,
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "PHP"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Code",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_a"
    }, {
        "id": 616,
        "question": "How do we check if a given variable is empty?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "With the null() function.",
            "answer_b": "With the empty() function.",
            "answer_c": "With the isitnull() function.",
            "answer_d": "With the isitempty() function.",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "PHP"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Code",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_b"
    }, {
        "id": 760,
        "question": "Which of the following function is used to read the content of a file?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "fopen()",
            "answer_b": "fread()",
            "answer_c": "filesize()",
            "answer_d": "file_exist()",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "PHP"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Code",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_b"
    }, {
        "id": 59,
        "question": "PHP server scripts are surrounded by delimiters, which?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "<&>...</&>",
            "answer_b": "<?php...?>",
            "answer_c": "<?php>...</?>",
            "answer_d": "<script>...</script>",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "PHP"
            }
        ],
        "category": "",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_b"
    }, {
        "id": 599,
        "question": "How are objects in PHP passed by?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "Objects are passed by value.",
            "answer_b": "Objects are passed by reference.",
            "answer_c": "Neither of the mentioned",
            "answer_d": null,
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "PHP"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Code",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_b"
    }, {
        "id": 604,
        "question": "Will a comparison of an integer 12 and a string \"13\" work in PHP?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "True",
            "answer_b": "False",
            "answer_c": null,
            "answer_d": null,
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "PHP"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Code",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_a"
    }
]
